这是他的尿布袋…
Okay,here's his diaper bag...
…跟他的闪闪先生
...and his Mr. Winky.
还有…
And...
…他，嗨！
... him. Hi!
一切都还好吗？ 好，很好
-How did everything go? -Great!
我们有个喷射性…
There was a projectile...
…呕吐事件，是他先开始的
...throwing up incident,but he started it.
我们得走了
We've gotta go.
对了
Oh,right.
我有个消息，是关于我们的
I've got some news. It's about us.
你跟我？
You and me?
不，苏珊跟我
No. Susan and me.
另一个“我们”
The other "us."
我们要结婚了
We're getting married.
就像“我现在宣布 你们成为妻子跟妻子”的“结婚”
As in,"I now pronounce you wife and wife" married?
我们欢迎你来，若你不想来 我们也完全了解
We'd like you to come. We understand if you don't want to.
我为什么会不想去呢？ 第一次婚礼我很开心
Why wouldn't I want to come? I had fun at the first wedding.
我想也许…
I just thought that
不…我是说… 我为什么不该替你高兴呢？
Why shouldn't I be happy for you? What would it say about me...
…如果我不能 为你的快乐而快乐
...if I couldn't revel in your joy?
那我算什么呢？ 我说的是真的，相信我
And I'm reveling,baby! Believe me!
你的手指被椅子夹住了吗？
Is your finger caught in that chair?
你要我们离开吗？
Want us to go?
六人行 第2季 第11集 同志婚礼
The One With the Lesbian Wedding
好酷耶 你真的要在电视上出现了
This is cool. You're actually on television.
我知道 我昨晚才真正的意识到
I know. It really hit me last night.
我要在 “我们的日子”里面演出了
I'm on Days of our Lives.
然后我开始想我们的事 我发现这正是“我们的日子”
Then I started thinking about us,and how these are the days of our lives.
太好了
Yes!
怎么了？
What?
帮卡萝跟苏珊办喜酒的人 这个周末骑登山车出了车祸…
Carol and Susan's caterer had a bike accident...
…全身都上了石膏
...and she's in a full-body cast.
他们要我办，这真太酷了吧 我从来没有搞过这个…
They asked me,which is cool since I've never catered...
…而且我很需要钱 这对你不会构成问题吧？
...and I need the money. Is this a problem?
那有关系吗？ 你太棒了
-Would it matter? -You're so great!
谢谢
Thank you!
你真的不去吗？ 我当然真的不去
-You're really not going? -I'm really not.
我不懂她们已经住在一起了 为什么还需要结婚？
They already live together. Why do they need to get married?
因为她们相爱啊
They love each other.
她们要跟她们亲密的人 一起庆祝那份爱
They wanna celebrate that love with the people close to them.
如果你硬要说那个理由的话
If you wanna call that a reason.
谁是客厅里最苦的人？
Who's the bitterest man in the living room?
客厅里最苦的男人？
The bitterest man in the living room?
嗨，邻居
Hi,neighbor.
罗斯，我以为你不在意了 那跟这个没有关系
-I thought you were over this. -That has nothing to do with it.
她是我前妻，要是嫁了一个男的话 你们不会希望我去
If she were marrying a guy,you wouldn't expect me to go.
她要是嫁了个男的话 她就成了史上最烂的同性恋了
If she were marrying a guy,she'd be the worst lesbian ever.
我错过了吗？
Did I miss it?
还没有，这个家伙自杀之后 我就上场了
No,I'm on right after this guy shoots himself.
她很漂亮耶
She's pretty.
对了，她人也很好
And she's really nice.
她教我怎么样在镜头前演戏…
She taught me about how to work with the cameras...
…还有“闻屁味”演戏法
...and smell-the-fart acting.
对不起？ 什么？
-I'm sorry,what? -Excuse me?
“闻屁味”演戏法
Smell-the-fart acting.
在短时间之内 要记那么多的台词…
You got so many lines to learn so fast that sometimes...
…有时候你需要时间想下一句
...you need a minute to remember your next one.
所以当你想的时候呢…
So while you're thinking...
…你停顿一下 表情装得非常的凝重
...you take this big pause where you look all intense.
像这样…
Like this....
轮到我了，我来了
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
瓦利斯太太？
Mrs. Wallace?
我是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生 你妹妹的神经外科医师
Dr. Drake Ramoray,your sister's neurosurgeon.
告诉我，她会不会好起来？
Is she going to be all right?
恐怕你妹妹的情形 比我们想像的还要糟糕
I'm afraid the situation is much more dire than we'd expected.
你妹妹得的病是…
Your sister's suffering from a...
…脑下血肿
...subcranial hematoma.
或许我们可以 边喝咖啡边聊一下
Perhaps we can discuss this further over coffee.
很好
Nice!
刚有那么一会儿，我还真以为 你闻到了什么东西呢
For a minute,I thought you were actually smelling something.
再来一次，演得太棒了 好…
-Do it again! -All right!
-That was so good! -Do it again.
“该死，贝弗曼 就在那张图表上”
"Damn it,Braverman! It's right there on the chart!"
太棒了，好了，我要去上班了 我有根大恐龙骨头要检查
I gotta get to work. I got a big dinosaur bone to inspect.
不…那是我
No,that's me.
对…你
Oh,right.
谢了，我没办法…
Oh,thanks. Couldn't....
你还好吧？
Is everything okay?
不
No.
今天我有一个客人 死在按摩桌上
One of my clients died on the massage table today.
天啊
Oh,my God!
你是不是让他们太放松了
That's a little more relaxed than you want them to get.
她已经八十二岁了…
She was,you know,82 years old...
…她叫爱德曼太太
...and her name was Mrs. Adelman.
亲爱的
Oh,honey.
对呀，感觉怪怪的…
It's just so strange. You know...
…她早上醒来时说不定在想…
...she probably woke up this morning and thought...
…我去吃点早餐，然后去散步 然后，再去按摩
... I'll have some breakfast,take a walk,then have my massage.
却不知道上帝在想 “好，但是就这样好了”
Little did she know God thought,"Okay,but that's it."
最诡异的事情是…
Oh,but the weirdest things was...
…发生的时候 我正在清她的灵气
... I was cleansing her aura when it happened.
当她的灵魂离开身体的时候…
And when her spirit left her body...
…我不认为它走远了
... I don't think it went very far.
什么意思啊？
What do you mean?
我想它上了我的身
I think it went into me.
这太难了
This is so hard.
我没有办法决定做羊还是鸭肉
I can't decide between lamb or duck.
当然了，羊肉比较恐怖
Well,lambs are scarier.
不然那部电影（《沉默的羔羊》）就会改为 “沉默的鸭子”了
Or the movie would've been called Silence of the Ducks.
好了，谁点了什么？
Okay,who ordered what?
我想我点了喝了一半 上面还有唇印的卡布奇诺咖啡
I had the half-drunk cappuccino with the lipstick on the rim.
对了，而这杯有烟屁股的 是无咖啡因的吗？
And this with the cigarette butt in it,is that decaf?
天哪
Oh,God.
真不敢相信 你妈要来会把你搞成这个样子
You're so uptight about your mom coming.
我知道，只是这是她第一次来 我不想她觉得…
I know. I just don't want her to think that because...
…因为我没嫁给贝瑞 我的生活就完全是垃圾
... I didn't marry Barry my life is crap.
说到垃圾 去听史黛拉尼德曼…
Talk about crap,just listen to Stella Neidman...
…一遍遍地讲她跟罗德斯泰格（影星）的故事
...tell her story about Rod Steiger for the hundredth time.
对不起，至少你们听不到她在我脑子里说的什么
I'm sorry. At least you guys don't have to hear what she says in my head.
菲比？ 你想她会跟我们在一起多久？
Pheebs? How long do you think this lady will be with us?
我不知道，老太太显然 还有什么心愿还没完成呢
I don't know. She obviously has some unfinished business.
坐好
Sit up!
她在这里
There she is!
妈妈 嘿，亲爱的
-Mom! -Hey,sweetie!
玛萝托马斯（影星）
Marlo Thomas
这就是你工作的地方啊
So this is where you work!
好棒啊
Oh,it's wonderful!
这是客厅吗？还是餐厅？ 谁看得出来？
Is it a living room? Is it a restaurant? Who can tell?
我猜乐趣就在那儿吧
I guess that's the fun.
差不多啦，来，看看我的朋友
Pretty much. Here,meet my friends.
莫妮卡，你看起来好美哟
Monica! You look gorgeous!
上回我看到你的时候 是在吃或是被吃呢？
Oh,my! The last time I saw you,it was eat or be eaten.
这是乔伊
This is Joey.
这是菲比
This is Phoebe.
这是钱德
This is Chandler.
你记得罗斯吧？
You remember Ross?
你好，罗斯
Oh,hello,Ross.
格林太太
Mrs. Greene.
你们认为我系着围裙…
What do you think of my daughter,in the apron...
…做大事的女儿怎么样？
...with the big job!
妈！
Oh,Mom!
没有你来倒咖啡呢 大家都休想喝到东西了
If you didn't pour the coffee,no one would have anything to drink.
相信我，有时候真的会这样的
Believe me,sometimes that happens.
太令人兴奋了 我从来没有做过事情
This is just so exciting! You know,I never worked.
我从我爸家 直接到女学生联谊会之家…
I went from my father's house to the sorority house...
…然后再到我先生的家 我以你为荣
...to my husband's house. I am just so proud of you!
-真的啊？-是的，让我把今天的行程计划一下
-Really?-Yes. Let's make a day of it.
我们去吃饭、购物，目标明确，做你想要的一切
We'll have lunch, shop, get our nails done. Whatever you want.
我必须工作
I have to work.
什么，没有别人可以倒咖啡吗？
What, no one else can pour coffee?
我知道你让我想起了谁了
I know who you remind me of.
艾沃琳德莫
Evelyn Durmer.
像去做大量的拉皮手术前的她 现在她像苏比赛尔了
That's before the lousy face-lift. Now she looks like Soupy Sales.
菲比，艾沃琳德莫是谁？
Pheebs? Who's Evelyn Durmer?
不知道，苏比赛尔是谁啊？
I don't know. Who's Soupy Sales?
老天啊
Oh,my God!
有个丑陋裸男在拉大提琴
There's an unattractive nude man playing the cello.
是啊，还好他不是 在拉一个比较小的乐器
Just be glad he's not playing a smaller instrument.
你的生活真有意思
You have some life here,sweetie!
妈，我知道你跟爸 很不高兴我没有嫁给贝瑞…
Mom,I realize you were upset when I didn't marry Barry...
…住在郊外的大房子 过着安逸的生活
...and get the house in the suburbs with all the security.
可是，这样对我好多了
This is just so much better for me.
我知道，你不爱贝瑞，亲爱的
I know. You didn't love Barry,honey.
我也没见过你这么快乐过
And I've never seen you this happy.
看着你，我心里在想… “这是我要的”
I look at you and I think,"This is what I want."
这是为我吗？
For me.
不只是为了你啦
Well,not just for you.
你是什么意思啊？
What do you mean?
我在考虑离开你爸爸
I'm considering leaving your father.
好，告诉我这是不是很可爱：
All right,tell me if this is too cute.
同性恋婚礼…，鸡胸肉
Lesbian wedding... chicken breasts.
天啊，我想我快吐了
Oh,God. I think I'm gonna be sick.
什么？ 我又没有在上面放小乳头
What? It's not like I'm putting little nipples on them.
亲爱的，很抱歉，请别生我的气
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.Please don't be mad at me.
我能做点什么？
What can I do?.
你想让我做你喜欢的棉花糖吗
You want me to make those marshmallow treats you used to like?.
我可以给卡梅拉打电话问问她怎么做
I can call up Carmela and find out how.
我不明白，我以为你一直很开心的
I don't understand.I thought you were happy.
是的，我也这么以为
Yeah, well, so did l.
想象一下很多次你在高速公路上开车
Know how sometimes you're driving on the highway...
回到家后却不记得曾到过那里
...and you get home and you can't remember having driven there?.
那就是我的生活状态
That's what my life's been like.
你能不能不要再听那些广播了
Well, couldn't you listen to the radio more?.
我希望能简简单单，但是我看到了你
I wish it were that easy.Then I see you...
我想，我为什么不能这样
...and I think,"Why can't I have this?. "
我想冒险，我想喝醉，我想要钱德
I want adventures, I want to hang out, I want a Chandler.
妈妈，相信我，钱德决不是你要离开爸爸的原因
Mom, believe me, Chandler is no reason to leave Daddy.
你以为我在享受乐趣吗，但是这真的很艰难，很艰难
You think I'm having fun,but it's really hard. Really hard.
我有一个讨厌的工作，我勉强支付房租，不去想买东西的事情
I've got a lousy job, I barely make rent, and forget about buying stuff!
亲爱的，你不明白
Oh, honey, you don't understand.
我跟你的处境一样，只不过我有钱而已
I'd be doing what you're doing,but with money.
这完全不同
It's very different.
你完全不知道他们处得不好 不知道
-You had no idea? -None.
他们不常吵架？
They didn't fight?
不，他们连话都不讲了
No,they didn't even talk to each other.
天啊，我怎么会知道 他们之间有问题啊
How was I suppose to know they were having problems?
在我那个时代 离婚不是个选择
You know,in my day,divorce was not an option.
看谁醒了
Hey,look who's up!
我只是无法相信这个事情嘛
I just can't believe this is happening!
我是说我小时候 每个人的父母都在闹离婚
When I was little,all parents got divorced.
我只是想，我长大了 就不用再担心这个了
I figured as an adult,I wouldn't have to worry about it.
你可不可以把这件事看做夸奖你呢？
Can't you look at this as flattering?
我是说 她这样做是想向你学习
She just wants to be like you.
那她不能 学我的发型就好了吗？
Well,couldn't she have just copied my haircut?
我父母离婚的时候 他们还叫我去看心理医生呢…
When my parents divorced,they sent me to a shrink...
…他们告诉我 所有的小孩都会怪自己
...and she told me that kids blame themselves.
就你而言，这真应该怪你呢
But in your case,it's actually kind of true.
就是他
Oh,that's him.
该死，我邮购的爷爷还没寄来
Damn! My mail-order grandfather hasn't come yet.
菲比？ 是，爱德曼先生
-Phoebe? -Hi,Mr. Adelman.
幸会，幸会 谢谢你来见我
-Nice to see you. -Thanks for coming.
没问题，不过你的确打扰了我 忙碌昏坐的一天
That's okay. Although you did cut into my busy day of sitting.
你要坐下来吗？
Do you wanna sit?
不…不用了 我早上花了好多时间才站起来
No,I spent most of my morning trying to stand up.
我能为你做些什么，亲爱的？
What can I do for you,my dear?
我不知道该怎么说啦…
Okay,I don't know how to say this,but....
当你太太的灵魂 离开她身体的时候…
I think when your wife's spirit left her body...
…她转入了我的…
...it kind of stuck around...
…身上
...in me.
你说我太太在你身上？
You're saying my wife is in you?
你用不着相信我啦…
Yeah. You don't have to believe me,but...
…不过你能想出她或许 有什么未完成的心愿吗？
...can you think of any unfinished business she had?
有什么原因让她留下来吗？
Any reason to hang around?
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say.
我唯一能够想到的是…
All I can think of is that...
…以前她常说她死之前 她想见识一切
...she used to say that before she died,she wanted to see everything.
一切？ 一切
-Everything? -Everything.
那可真是不少
That's a lot of stuff.
等一等…
Oh,wait,l....
我想起来了，她还说 她想最后再跟我上一次床
I remember she also said she wanted to sleep with me one last time.
对不起，我脑袋里有笑声
I'm sorry. There's laughing in my head.
值得一试吧，对吧
Worth a shot,huh?
看这一张
Look at this!
-这是三年前万圣节的照片-我的小马提尼（鸡尾酒）
-These are all Halloween,three years ago.-My little martini
我喜欢你橄榄色的头发
I love your olive head.
你看，这是贝瑞
Oh,and look,here's Barry.
他直接从诊所过来吗？
He came straight from the office?
不，那是他的变装
Oh,no. That was his costume.
他是个牙齿矫正师 但他打扮成一般的牙医
See,he's actually an orthodontist,but he came as a regular dentist.
是的，他以为那很搞笑
Yeah, he thought that was really funny.
各位
You guys?
记得我以前说 谢了，我不需要你们帮忙？
Remember when I said that I don't need your help?
事实上，我想你说的是…
Actually,I think you said...
…“别乱碰 离我的厨房远一点”
... "Don't touch that and get out of my kitchen."
真的？奇怪，不过…
Really? Weird. Anyway....
我一切都计划得很好 我计划计划又计划
I planned really well. I planned and planned.
只是我想 我实际烹饪的时间计划得不够
I just didn't plan enough time to do it.
莫妮卡，需要帮忙吗？ 如果你想的话
-You want some help? -lf you want.
好长的一天
What a day!
我带这位老太太到处去逛
I took her everywhere.
我们去了现代美术馆 洛克菲勒中心…
The Museum of Modern Art,Rockefeller Center...
…自由女神像
...the Statue of Liberty.
她还跟着你啊？
She's still with you?
对呀，我猜这位老太太 还没见过一切呢
Yes. I guess she hasn't seen everything yet.
我马上回来 她必须再去一趟厕所
Be right back. She has to go to the bathroom again.
一张好漂亮的脸
Such a pretty face!
这好好玩，就只有我们女生
Oh,this is so much fun! Just the girls!
知道我们该做什么吗？ 我想请问一下，谁有大麻？
Do you know what we should do? Does anybody have any marijuana?
天啊
God!
刚才我妈妈是问了我们有没有大麻吗？
Did my mother just ask if we have pot?.
听着 不准在这堆食物旁边吸大麻
Look,no one's smoking pot around all this food.
没关系
Well,that's fine.
我从没抽过，只想试一试
I never did it. I just thought I might.
那么…最近的性事是什么？
What's new in sex?
最近的性事是什么？
我只跟你老爸做过那件事而已
The only man I've been with is your father.
我切我切切切，我啥也没听到
I'm dicing. I'm dicing. I don't hear anything.
我不是在批评你爸爸，亲爱的 我只是在想…
This is no offense to your dad,but I was thinking...
…或许不只是那样而已
...there might be more.
对不起，你知道吗？ 我没有办法跟你谈这件事
You know what? I cannot have this conversation with you.
好啊…
All right.
你甚至还没告诉爸 就到我这里来丢这颗炸弹
You come here and drop this bomb on me before you even tell Daddy.
你想要我的祝福吗？想让我劝你别这样吗？
Do you want my blessing? Want me to talk you out of it?
你到底要什么？
Then what do you want?
我猜我以为 在所有人当中你最了解我
I guess I figured you would understand.
为什么我应该要最了解你呢？
Why on earth would I understand this?
你没有嫁给你的贝瑞
You didn't marry your Barry,honey.
但是我嫁了我的贝瑞
But I married mine.
好了，各位，我们来不及了 我们只剩下12小时又36分
We're in trouble. We've only got 12 hours and 36 minutes left.
快…
Move,move,move!
莫妮卡，我觉得 你应该加上德文字幕才对
I feel like you should have German subtitles.
乔伊，快一点嘛
Joey,speed it up!
抱歉，是猪啦 它们不愿意进毯子啊
I'm sorry! It's the pigs! They're reluctant to get in the blanket!
莫妮卡，怎么会这样呢？ 我以为你全部都计划好了
How did this happen? I thought you had this planned out.
你要我哭吗？
Do you want me to cry?
那就是你要的吗？
Is that what you want?
你要看到我哭吗？
Do you wanna see me cry?
长官，不要，长官
Sir,no,sir!
好了，你
All right,you!
不，我说过我不参与这件事
No. Look,I told you,I am not a part of this thing.
我知道你跟卡萝和苏珊有过节 我很同情你，真的
Look,Ross. I know you have issues with Carol and Susan,and I feel for you.
但是如果你不帮我 我会用一堆热狗…
But if you don't help,I'm gonna take those hot dogs...
…创造出一道 新的开胃菜叫“罗斯猪肉卷”
...and create an appetizer called "Pigs In Ross."
好，挖香瓜球
All right,ball a melon!
为什么我得切丁 他却可以挖香瓜球呢？
How come I'm stuck dicing when he gets to ball a melon?
进行得怎么样？ 非常顺利，全按时间来
-How's it going? -Great! Right on schedule.
有我快乐的小帮手们 是啊
Got my little happy helpers.
很好啊
That's fine. Whatever.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.
好吧，所有的事 我想我们婚礼要取消了
Okay,everything. I think we're calling off the wedding.
你还是会付我钱的吧？
You're still gonna pay me,right?
或是做不那么自私的事
Or something a little less selfish.
卡萝，发生什么事了？
What's the matter? What happened?
我爸妈今天下午来电话 说他们不来了
My parents called to say they weren't coming.
我是说 我知道他们不赞成这件事…
I knew they were having trouble with this,but...
…可是他们是我父母啊 他们应该把我嫁出去的
...they're my parents. They're supposed to give me away.
然后我跟苏珊大吵了一架 因为我说或许应该取消婚礼
Susan and I fought because I said maybe we should call it off.
然后她说“这不是为了他们 这是为了我们”
She said,"This isn't for them. It's for us."
“如果我不了解这个的话 或许我们真应该取消婚礼”
And if I couldn't see that,we should cancel the wedding.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
不相信我要这么说 但我认为苏珊是对的
I can't believe I'm gonna say this,but I think Susan's right.
真的？
You do?
你爱她吗？ 你不用说得太斩钉截铁
Do you love her? And don't be too emphatic about this.
我当然爱她了
Of course I do.
那就是了
Well then,that's it.
如果你的父母无法接受的话 那就去他们的
If George and Adelaide can't accept that,then the hell with them.
听着，我是说 若我的父母不要我娶你的话…
If my parents didn't want me to marry you...
…那绝对阻止不了我
... no way that would've stopped me.
这是你的婚礼
Look,this is your wedding.
去做
Do it.
说得对，当然你是对的
You're right. Of course you're right.
那我们继续吗？
So we're back on?
我们继续吧
We're back on.
你们听到了，削皮，剁，切
You heard the woman! Peel! Chop! Devil!
真不敢相信我停了两分钟
Can't believe I lost two minutes!
我真的觉得好白费心机
It just seems so futile.
你看，这么多女人跟没有一样
You know? All these women,and nothing!
我觉得自己像没了神力的超人
I feel like Superman without my powers,you know?
我有披风，但我飞不起来
I have the cape,and yet I cannot fly.
现在你应该知道 我每天单身的感觉了吧
Well,now you understand how I feel every single day.
世界是我的同性恋婚礼
The world is my lesbian wedding.
奶油糖？
Butterscotch?
有人要吃吗？
No one?
好吧，待会儿你们会后悔的
All right,you'll be sorry later.
谢谢 随时为你
-Thank you. -Anytime.
罗斯
Ross.
没有任何一件事…
Nothing makes God happier...
…比两个人 因爱而结合使上帝更快乐
...than when two people,any two people,come together in love.
我们今日齐聚一堂…
Friends,family,we're gathered here today...
…见证卡萝和苏珊神圣的婚礼
...to join Carol and Susan in holy matrimony.
老天
Oh,my God!
现在我看全所有的事情了
Now I've seen everything!
她走了
She's gone!
她…她走了
她走了
She's gone.
来吧，结婚啊
Go ahead,get married. Go,go!
黑夜中的陌生人
Strangers in the night
目光交会
Exchanging glances
在黑夜中游荡
Wondering in the night
你看看她们
Would you look at them?
是啊，忍不住…
Yeah. Can't help but.
那道猪肉卷好不好吃啊？
How's that pig-in-the-blanket working out for you?
是我把这些坏孩子卷起来的
I wrapped those bad boys.
我想念露丝
I miss Rose.
是吗？
Oh,yeah?
我知道这有点怪怪的 但是她是我生活的一部分…
I know it's kind of weird,but she was a big part of my life....
我只是觉得有点孤单
I don't know,I feel alone.
我听到你刚说的话
You know,I couldn't help overhearing what you just said.
我想你也该把露丝抛在脑后了 继续你的生活
I think it's time you forget about Rose,move on with your life.
我们去拿杯饮料如何？
How about we get you a drink?
好的，你真好
Okay. So nice!
我连搭讪的话都不用讲了 是不是？
I shouldn't even bother coming up with a line,right?
妈，好玩吗？
Hey,Mom,having fun?
太好玩了，我刚才跟一个 好高大的女人跳舞
Am l! I just danced with a wonderfully large woman.
另外有三个女孩 在自助餐那边对我眨眼睛
And three other girls made eyes at me over at the buffet.
我不是说这是我所要追求的…
I'm not saying it's something I wanna pursue...
…但是知道有选择好令人欣慰
... but it's nice to know I have options.
还有酒，对吧？
There's more alcohol,right?
你好吗？
How you doing?
你今天做了件好事
You did a good thing today.
想跳舞吗？
You wanna dance?
不，算了
No,that's fine.
来嘛
Come on.
我让你带舞
I'll let you lead.
谁在乎阴茎
Look,penis,schmenis!
我们都是人
Okay? We're all people.
你们想 我们之中哪一个会先结婚？
Which one of us is gonna be the first one to get married?
莫妮卡，我已经结过婚了
Mon,I was married.
我也是，理论上来说。-我有过婚礼
-Yeah,me too,technically. -I had a wedding.
好啊 只是想开始个有趣的讨论
Just trying to start a discussion.
我想到了 哪一个会最晚结婚？
Which one do you think will be the last to get married?
你们说小班算不算？
Isn't Ben in this?
算哪
Of course!
当然算了
Absolutely.